// Need to establish arrays containing questions, possible answers, and correct answer. Start with five, more if time allows
// Keep this separate, actual js will be complicated enough

var questions = [{
	"question": "MGS1 featured Solid Snake infiltrating which island?",
	"option1": "Fireball Island",
	"option2": "Shadow Moses",
	"option3": "Kokomo",
	"option4": "Hawaii",
	"answer": 2
}, {
	"question": "The remote-controlled missile is known by which nickname?",
	"option1": "Panther",
	"option2": "S.A.M.",
	"option3": "Javelin",
	"option4": "Nikita",
	"answer": 4
}, {
	"question": "The Next-Generation Special Forces who took part in the uprising with FOXHOUND were given what treatment?",
	"option1": "Gene Therapy",
	"option2": "Electroshock",
	"option3": "Psychological",
	"option4": "Radiation",
	"answer": 1
}, {
	"question": "On which floor of the Nuclear Warhead Storage Building was the lab of Dr. Hal Emmerich located?",
	"option1": "Main Floor",
	"option2": "Basement",
	"option3": "Second Floor Basement",
	"option4": "Third Floor",
	"answer": 3
}, {
	"question": "What was the true identity of the Cyborg Ninja?",
	"option1": "Frank Martin",
	"option2": "Frank Reynolds",
	"option3": "Frank Jaeger",
	"option4": "Frank Sinatra",
	"answer": 3
}, {
	"question": "What item must you wear to have infinite ammunition?",
	"option1": "Crocodile Hat",
	"option2": "Bandana",
	"option3": "Cheetah Fatigues",
	"option4": "Cardboard Box",
	"answer": 2
}, {
	"question": "How does Vulcan Raven die?",
	"option1": "He steps on a Claymore mine",
	"option2": "He is eaten alive by ravens",
	"option3": "His car loses traction on a banana peel and goes off a cliff",
	"option4": "He falls down an elevator shaft",
	"answer": 2
}, {
	"question": "What affects the shape of the PAL card?",
	"option1": "Temperature",
	"option2": "Electrical impulse",
	"option3": "Saturation level",
	"option4": "Light intensity",
	"answer": 1
}, {
	"question": "How do you acquire the Stealth item?",
	"option1": "Survive electrocution",
	"option2": "Beat Revolver Ocelot with hand-to-hand combat",
	"option3": "Beat the entire game without using a ration",
	"option4": "Submit during electrocution",
	"answer": 4
}, {
	"question": "What is the name of the largest weapon that Snake fights against in MGS1?",
	"option1": "Metal Gear REX",
	"option2": "Metal Gear RAY",
	"option3": "Arsenal Gear",
	"option4": "Shagohod",
	"answer": 1
}]	